Hello friends, my name is Anand Bansal
and today we will be discussing [music] about ICICI lb's Elevate Plan as part of Square Insurance.in's Know
Your Plan series.
First of all, the
minimum age limit to take this plan is 18 years.  There
is no maximum age limit.  A person of any age group can
take this plan.  The
minimum sum assured in this plan is ₹5 lakh.  There
is no limit on the maximum sum insured.  That means
you
can take this plan for unlimited sum insured.  There is no room rent limit in this plan [Music].  There is
no limit on ICU also.  If for any reason you
need to be hospitalized, then
this plan provides you cover for 90 days before admission to the hospital and 180 days after discharge from the hospital.  There is
no copayment in this plan.  That means the insurance company makes the
full payment to you.  This plan
offers you the facility of No Claim Bonus
which is 20% of sum insured every year.
But this plan has a unique feature
called Power Booster.  If you
purchase Power Booster by paying additional premium,
you get 100% No Claim Bonus guaranteed every year.
For example [music] if
your policy is for ₹1 lakh and you have
taken Power Booster add-on, then every year your
policy will increase by ₹10 lakh and
you will continue to get this no claim benefit as long as your policy is in force.
This plan has three unique
features which make it different from others.
The first feature is Infinite
Care which means you can make
any single claim for any amount during your policy year.
Suppose you have
taken a sum insured of ₹1 lakh.  But if
your claim is even ₹1 crore, you
can request the insurer to
settle your claim of ₹1 crore.
Another unique feature of this plan is Infinite Sum
Insured.  This means you do
not need to worry about the sum insured.  You
can choose unlimited sum insured.   The
third unique feature of this plan is Jump
Start.  That means, if you have any pre-existing disease like asthma, blood
pressure, cholesterol, diabetes or obesity,
then by
paying additional premium, you
can get coverage for these diseases from the 31st day.  This
plan gives you the facility of unlimited restoration
which is infinite time.
If [MUSIC] for any reason you have a
claim and your sum insured is reduced
, your base sum insured will be
restored.  For example, if you have
taken a policy of Rs 10 lakh and your first
claim is Rs 5 lakh, then your balance sum
insured is Rs 1 lakh.  But if
any insured person needs the sum insured in the same year,
your Rs 5 lakh will be
restored and you can claim up to Rs 1 lakh
again [Music].  This
plan offers you the facility of Claim Protector
under which you can get payment for
68 non-consumable items mentioned in List One.
In this plan, you can reduce the
waiting period for your pre-existing disease
from 3 years to 2 years or 1 year [music] by paying additional premium.
This plan
also provides you the facility of OPD benefit on paying additional premium.
You
can also get maternity cover by paying additional premium in this plan.
[Music] There are many more unique features like this
that you can discuss in detail with our agents or
our employees.
Through squireinsurance.in you
can get dedicated tele relationship manager
claim assistance and you can also get detailed information
about the plan by calling a Squire Insurance advisor at your home.
squire insurance.in [Music]
Policy Endorsement Claim Renewal Now everything is
easy.